uwo.ca 2005-12-15

# Privacy Office

Welcome to the official Web site of the Privacy Office at The University of Western Ontario.

This site contains information about Western’s privacy protection strategy and initiatives. As it evolves, it will provide specific guidance to faculty and staff who collect, use and disclose personal information on behalf of the University in the course of their authorized activities. It will also enable anyone whose personal information is maintained by Western to learn more about what steps are being taken to protect his or her privacy.

As noted in the Overview, in its effort to continue to protect the personal information of all individuals who come into contact with the University, Western has chosen to adopt a broadly based ‘privacy protection’ strategy. Rather than focusing exclusively on the specific requirements of new federal privacy legislation, our goal at Western is to ensure that all personal information is dealt with appropriately.

If you have any questions or concerns about Western’s approach to protecting personal information please visit the Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) page or contact us directly. Contact information is provided elsewhere on this site.

I look forward to working with members of Western’s community to ensure that we continue to protect the personal information that is entrusted to our care. 

Sincerely,

**Robin Keirstead**  
_University Commissioner for Access to Information and Privacy Protection_

Also from this web page:

## Questions?

Questions about Western’s approach to protecting personal information should be directed to:

**Robin Keirstead**  
519-850-2300 

* * *
